five9.com 2013-06-27

# Privacy Policy

### FIVE9 WEB SITE PRIVACY STATEMENT

**Last Updated: February 4, 2013**

Thank you for visiting the Five9, Inc. web site (the “Site”). Five9 respects your privacy and we have created this privacy statement (“Privacy Statement”) to help you understand what information we collect and how that information is used. Your use of the Site is governed by this Privacy Statement. This Privacy Statement applies only to data collected by Five9 through the Site and does not apply to data provided to Five9 by any other means, such as in connection with services provided by Five9 to customers under specific agreements between Five9 and the customer.

### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We collect information from you when you use the Site with or without registration, upon registration and when you place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey. Upon registration and in connection with placing an order, you may be asked to enter certain personal information, such as your first and last name, email address, physical address, company name, phone number and username and password. You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of the information you submit to Five9 in connection with your use of the Site. If you use the Site without registration, the only information we collect will be non-personal information related to your IP address, web browser and operating system information.

### WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?

The information we collect from you in connection with the Site may be used in one or more of the following ways: to customize and personalize your experience using the Site (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs); to improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs); and to send communications to you, including emails. By registering, you consent to Five9 sending you communications and marketing materials related to services or products provided to you by Five9 or that may otherwise be of interest to you, including services or products of our partners or third parties. You will have an opportunity to opt-out of receiving marketing communications by following the instructions provided on the communication.

### DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES

We do not sell or trade your personal information to third parties. We share certain categories of information we collect from you with trusted third parties that assist us in operating the Site, conducting our business or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep your information secure and confidential. We also reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when disclosure is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on the Site or Five9.

### NOTICE TO RESIDENTS OF COUNTRIES OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA

Five9 is headquartered in the United States. We recognize that other countries and the European Community have established data protection regimes which may be more protective of any data you may provide. If you live outside the United States, by using the Site and providing information to us through the Site, including upon registration, you agree and consent to our collection, transfer, and processing of such data in accordance with this Privacy Statement. When you use the Site or provide information, you are solely responsible for compliance with any data protection or privacy obligations in your jurisdiction.

### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

The Site contains links to other third party websites. Five9 is not responsible for the privacy practices of such third-party websites. We strongly recommend that you review the privacy policy of each website that you access prior to providing any personal information to make sure you understand what data is collected and how such data is used by third parties.

### UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you wish to modify personal information previously provided on the Site, or if you have any questions regarding this Privacy Statement or this Site, please contact:

Attn: Marketing Department  
4000 Executive Parkway Suite 400  
San Ramon, CA 94583  
United States  

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

We occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect changes in our products and services and customer feedback. When we post changes, we revise the “last updated” date at the top of this statement. Your use of the Site is subject to the then effective Privacy Statement.
